------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------V 1.0------------------------------
--------Bearded Bandits Info/Help/Tips--------
--------Free the People, Free the World!--------
----------------------------jewbmx@gmail.com-------
--------------------------------------------------------------------

(This help file is hosted online so it can be updated.)
(Check the top for the current app version released.)

*Need help or wanna contact me for any other reaaon? feel free to email me.
(If you would like a custom list or anything added to the app then hit me up.)

*Wanna shut this Help option off and remove it from the Main Menu?
(Goto settings and disable the Help Dialog. app looks better without it lol.)

*Clear the Cache every once in a while. Its in the app Settings under its own Tab.
---Also located in the Quick Tools Menu for easy access.
(Once a week or month is Advised.)
(If the app laggs alot then it might be time.)
(I clear mine every day but thats me.)

*Little trick that works most the time is to click play on the same item again after it fails.
---The second attempt usually pulls with less work and can find a source easier. 
(Doesn't work 100% of the time. meant for stuff that you know should be available.)
---Also for when you find those 'rare' mismatch items to watch/play.
(like the movie 'Unforgiven' by C. Eastwood from 1992 gets scrambled with the 2013 Japanese one by Lee Sang.)
(another is TV Show 'Bunnicula' has messed up season lists in alot of addons and plays the wrong episode sometimes.)
---If a movie doesnt play or cant find any sources just wait a few days or check its release date. Problem might be that simple.

*Addons like this one and many others are quite busy doing alot of stressful stuff. take your time and be chill.
(Try to imagine a 3-5 second cooldown timer after any command is done to help prevent errors and crashes.)
 
*If you click something and your sitting around still waiting after 2 minutes have passed, then its probably safe to say that the choice failed.
(Could also be a Cache issue. Unless your just too high and didnt even click anything but thought you did lol. which can happens quite often.)

*First glance thru the options and your like damn why so many sources? easy because why not.
---Some sources dont have what i want so i check the next source, and most the time find what i want lol.
(getting it to play is another story lol. rip to all the great classics that are hard to find.)


-----Settings-----
*The Settings for this app are(should be) set up as a 2 click auto play. 1st one to start the process, 2nd for hd/sd choice.

*Want to stop selecting hd or sd every time? Change the Select Link setting to your choice instead of Both.

*Want to choose the site you watch from? Enable the link selection dialog Setting in the Scrapers Tab.

*The link selection fallthrough Setting in the Scrapers Tab is very handy and advised to stay Enabled.
(Makes life much easier.)

*In the Settings Resolvers Tab there are a few options you can Enable in the 'Filtering Options' if you want more streaming sources.
(I keep all the Filtering Options Disabled personally. Those are the sources that need you to pair your shit.)
(sometimes one might slip through the fliter, just hit cancel if it happens.)

*The API Settings are important and already setup with my API's. Dont remove them unless you have your own to put in.
 (Sort of advanced and not something a normal user should have to mess with.)
 
 
-----Standard Info-----
*The Main Menu options like Movies and TV Shows are mostly filled with just scrapper stuff like a common app.
---Added the best TV Show option ever called CatchUp Calendar.
---Added 2018, 2019, and 2020 to Years section for a head start on great movies.

*The CarToon Section houses a huge ammount of anime, cartoons, movies, and about anything else child friendly.
---Made sure not to add my bottom menu bar to this section so the kiddos cant go clicking away.
---Went ahead and labeled the options that are large lists for you so you can be prepared lol.

*The JewZone Section is where you will find all the special stuff. Plus my favorite stuff too.
 ---The JewZone Menu features a custom tv networks list, made up of my favorite networks.
(broken down into mutiple lists so i could place them in the other rightful places for ease.)
(Theres also a Web Channels list from TVmaze because its awesome sauce.)
---Theres a special page in JewZone called DC / Marvel thats a collection of public lists dedicated to their title.
---Another one is called My Top5 Trakt Users. which is what it sounds like but all their lists lol.
(Note: these are very well done lists and seem to stay maintained.)
(A great thanks from me to each person that made em cause they are dope.)
---The Hulu/Netflix/Amazon page is exactly what it says and is made up of fantastic lists.
---Added a page called The Future that is hosted online for easy modifcations without annoying updates.
(all user requested content will be here, along with any custom or new stuff that i decide to add.)
---Jew Top 250 TV Shows: is a list of my favorite shows that ive watched and would recommend to others.
(Wont change but new shows are sure to come around and be added to a new list due to size.)
---JewFlix: is my version of a Recently Added list and Movie Rental Service. 
(Updated monthly with a new random list of recommended movies. Both new and old.)
---JewWatchList: is what im watching lately lol.
(Updated randomly when I find new stuff to watch and cleaned weekly.)
---JewList: is a huge collection of all my favorite movies ever seen. might be missing a few but they will be remembered lol.
(Note that this list is huge so it might load a little slow and be a pain to get thru.)
---Also tossed in a page that shows ya all my Trakt lists too, incase i make a few new ones.

*Fair warning for those who read this far, there is a Adult section hidden in this addon.
(I have another addon in my repo that is the CarToon section of this addon if needed.)

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
