--------------------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------V 1.0------------------------------
--------Bearded Bandits Info/Help/Tips--------
--------Free the People, Free the World!--------
----------------------------jewbmx@gmail.com-------
--------------------------------------------------------------------

*This Help Page is hosted online and will be auto updated when i change things.
(Check the top for the current app version released.)

*Check out the Quick Help section if you need more information or help thats not here.

*Need help or wanna contact me for any other reaaon? feel free to email me.
(If you would like a custom list or anything added to the app then hit me up.)
 
*Wanna shut this Help option off and remove it from the Main Menu?
(Goto settings and disable the Help Dialog lol. app looks better without it.)
 
*Clear the Cache every once in a while. Its in the app Settings under its own Tab.
(Once a week or month is Advised. If the app laggs alot then it might be time. I clear mine every day but thats me.)

*Little trick that works most the time is to click play on the same item again after it fails.
---The second attempt usually pulls with less work and can find a source easier. 
(Doesn't work 100% of the time. meant for stuff that you know should be available.)
---Also for when you find those 'rare' mismatch items to watch/play.
(like the movie 'Unforgiven' by C. Eastwood from 1992 gets scrambled with the 2013 Japanese one by Lee Sang.)
(another is TV Show 'Bunnicula' has messed up season lists in alot of addons and plays the wrong episode sometimes.)

*Addons like this one and many others are quite busy doing alot of stressful stuff. take your time and be chill.
(Try to imagine a 3-5 second cooldown timer after any command is done to help prevent errors and crashes.)

*TMDB is slow at loading most the time so other sources are advised. Also depends on list sizes.
(In my mind show source speeds go TvMaze, Trakt, then TMDB and IMDB. I choose them in that order as well.)
 
*If you click something and your sitting around still waiting after 2 minutes have passed, then its probably safe to say that the choice failed.
(Could also be a Cache issue. Unless your just too high and didnt even click anything but thought you did lol. which can happens quite often.)

