------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------V 1.0------------------------------
-------------ToonTopia Info/Help/Tips-------------
--------Free the People, Free the World!--------
----------------------------jewbmx@gmail.com-------
--------------------------------------------------------------------

(This help file is hosted online so it can be updated.)
(Check the top for the current app version released.)
(This is a more kid friendly version of  the CarToon section in Bearded Bandit.)

*Need help or wanna contact me for any other reaaon? feel free to email me.
(If you would like a custom list or anything added to the app then hit me up.)

*Wanna shut this Help option off and remove it from the Main Menu?
(Goto settings and disable the Help Dialog. app looks better without it lol.)

*Might want to go through the settings and modify them so theres no popups or extra steps to play something.
(Would be good for tossing your kid control.)

*Clear the Cache every once in a while. Its in the app Settings under its own Tab.
---Also located in the Quick Tools Menu for easy access.
(Once a week or month is Advised.)
(If the app laggs alot then it might be time.)
(I clear mine every day but thats me.)

*Little trick that works most the time is to click play on the same item again after it fails.
---The second attempt usually pulls with less work and can find a source easier. 
(Doesn't work 100% of the time. meant for stuff that you know should be available.)
---Also for when you find those 'rare' mismatch items to watch/play.
(like the movie 'Unforgiven' by C. Eastwood from 1992 gets scrambled with the 2013 Japanese one by Lee Sang.)
(another is TV Show 'Bunnicula' has messed up season lists in alot of addons and plays the wrong episode sometimes.)
---If something doesnt play or cant find any sources just wait a few days or check its release date. Problem might be that simple.

*Addons like this one and many others are quite busy doing alot of stressful stuff. take your time and be chill.
(Try to imagine a 3-5 second cooldown timer after any command is done to help prevent errors and crashes.)


-----Settings-----
*The Settings for this app are(should be) set up as a 2 click auto play. 1st one to start the process, 2nd for hd/sd choice.

*Want to stop selecting hd or sd every time? Change the Select Link setting to your choice instead of Both.

*Want to choose the site you watch from? Enable the link selection dialog Setting in the Scrapers Tab.

*The link selection fallthrough Setting in the Scrapers Tab is very handy and advised to stay Enabled.
(Makes life much easier.)

*In the Settings Resolvers Tab there are a few options you can Enable in the 'Filtering Options' if you want more streaming sources.
(I keep all the Filtering Options Disabled personally. Those are the sources that need you to pair up.)
(sometimes one might slip through the fliter, just hit cancel if it happens.)

*The API Settings are important and already setup with my API's. Dont remove them unless you have your own to put in.
 (Sort of advanced and not something a normal user should have to mess with.)

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
