
------------------------------V 1.0------------------------------
----------Bearded Bandits Help and Tips----------

*This Help Page is hosted online and will be auto updated when i change things. check the top for the current app version released.

*Need help or wanna contact me for any other reaaon? feel free to email me  jewbmx@gmail.com  .
(fair warning- if your email goes to spam i wont see it lol. try not to seem like a bot. its rare but beware.)
*If you would like a custom list or anything added to the app then hit me up. i can also send you a custom version if youd like.

*Wanna shut this Help option off and remove it from the Main Menu?
(Goto settings and disable the Help Dialog lol. app looks better without it.)

*Clear the Cache every once in a while. Its in the app Settings under its own Tab. Once a week or month is Advised. I clear mine every day but thats me.
(Once started it will pop up different 'plugins' that you can choose not to clear the cache on. feel free to mash yes.)

*First time page loads and after a cleansing of the cache are very often slow to load. Its usually just all the extra info and crap loading.

*If you click something and your sitting around still waiting after 2 minutes have passed, its safe to say that the choice failed and you gotta try another.
(unless your just too high and didnt even click anything but thought you did lol. which can happens quite often.)

---Settings---
-The Settings for this app are(should be) set up as a 2 click auto play. 1st one to start the process, 2nd for hd/sd choice.
-The Meta Settings are optional and you can turn em on or off depending on how you want em.
-Want to choose the site you watch from? Enable the link selection dialog Setting in the Scrapers Tab.
-The link selection fallthrough Setting in the Scrapers Tab is very handy and advised to stay Enabled.
-In the Settings Resolvers Tab there are a few options you can Enable in the 'Filtering Options' if you want more streaming sources.
-I keep all the Filtering Options Disabled personally.
-The API Settings are important and already setup with my API's. Dont remove them unless you have your own to put in.

---Standard Info---
-The Main Menu options like Movies and TV Shows are mostly filled with just scrapper stuff like a common app.
-First glance thru the options and your like damn why so many sources? easy because why not.
-Some sources dont have what i want so i check the next source, and most the time find what i want lol.

-The Main Menu option called JewZone is where you will find all the special stuff.
-Theres a special page in JewZone called DC / Marvel that is a collection of public lists dedicated to their title.
(Note: these are very well done lists and seem to stay maintained. a great thanks from me to each person that made em cause they are dope.)

-TMDB is slow at loading most the time so other sources are advised.
-In my mind show source speeds go TvMaze, Trakt, then TMDB and IMDB. I choose them in that order as well.

---Movies---
-Added 2018, 2019, and 2020 to Years section for a head start on great movies.
-If a movie doesnt play or cant find any sources just wait a few days or check its release date. Problem might be that simple.



